《猛鬼街5：猛鬼怪胎》
70  71
Seventy, seventy one...
- 快一点  好吗  - 闭嘴
- Come on, will you? - Shut up.
你害我忘记数到哪里了
You're making me lose the count.
Seventy-two.
差不多了  已经有一百个人了
Close enough. It's a hundred.
我们走吧
Let's go.
不  等一下
No, wait!
不
No!
艾莉丝  醒一醒
Hey, hey, hey. Alice, Alice, wake up. Hey.
天啊
Jesus.
成年后我们得准备迎接新生活
And as adults, we must now prepare for a new life...
离开一直保护着我们的春木高中
...outside this wonderful environment known as Springwood High.
大家加油吧
So let's blow this pop stand.
艾莉丝  伊芳
Alice. Yvonne.
你是怎么了  我们得笑一个
What's wrong with you? Let's see a smile.
我昨晚累坏了
I had kind of a long night.
丹又不让你睡  姊妹  你得把窗户锁好
Dan keeping you up again? Girl, you better put a lock on that window.
丹还蛮猛的
The Dan part was nice.
这真的很疯狂  你们觉得呢
These things are wild. What do you think?
- 你看起来很像修女  - 急着违背她的誓约
- You look like a nun. - Dying to break her vows.
帮我找个男人
Find me a man.
太棒了
Fabulous.
- 或许我该说得仔细点  - 或许是上帝给你的启示
- Maybe I should spell it out for you. - Maybe God's trying to tell you something.
- 你何时要跟我私奔  - 下辈子再说吧
- When are you gonna run away with me? - Next life.
- 那是什么  - 我不放弃的爱
- What's that? - My undying love.
- 吃吧 - 哈哈
- Have some. - Ha, ha.
马克  放弃吧  那是没用的
Mark, give it up. It's hopeless.
不  我想我开始打动她了
No, no. I think I'm starting to wear her down.
吃一口吧
Have a taste, anyway.
葛芮姐  封面女郎不吃那个的
Greta, that's not what a cover girl puts in her body.
- 该死  - 她看穿了你的心思
- Shit. - Mm. She read you.
美女们  今晚到哪里庆祝
Ladies, ladies, where's the party tonight?
我们何不到艾莉丝家玩呢
Why don't we go to Alice's?
不  我爸不喜欢有人在家里喝酒
No. My dad's got this thing about drinking in the house.
- 我们得想个点子  - 听我说  各位
- Well, we gotta do something. - Listen, guys.
我得练游泳  游到明天六点半
I got swimming practice until 6:30 tomorrow.
- 所以呢  - 他们得给我钥匙
- So? - That means they're gonna give me the key.
我才能在练完后锁门
So I can lock up after I'm done.
泳池派对
Pool party.
- 好吧  - 我喜欢
- All right. - I like that.
该死  今晚我得上班
Oh, damn, I gotta work tonight.
马克  拍照了
Hey, Mark, picture time.
快过来留下永恒的记忆  父母跟小鬼
Come and get immortalized. Parents and brats. Ha-ha-ha.
葛芮姐  该拍照了  亲爱的
Greta, photo opportunity, dear.
该死  被他们抓到了
Damn, they caught me.
现在我得为狗仔队露齿而笑
I have to go gnash my teeth for the paparazzi.
你们先去吧  待会我再去找你们
You go on ahead. I'll catch up with you later.
- 好吧  再见  - 好吧
- Okay. See you. - Okay.
- 再见  - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
好
Okay.
嗨  艾莉丝
Hi, Alice.
- 美女  - 天啊  别吓我
- Hey, beautiful. - Oh, Jesus, don't do that.
抱歉  我有礼物送你
Sorry. I got a present for you.
- 你弄到机票了  - 对
- You got the tickets. - Yeah.
虽然是经济舱  但这班飞机会在巴黎停靠
They're coach seats, but, uh, this plane stops in Paris.
- 这会是非常棒的暑假  - 对  我知道
- It's gonna be a great summer. - Yeah, I know.
怎么了
Hey. What's the matter?
没事  我在毕业典礼上没看到我爸
Nothing. It's just I didn't see my dad at the ceremony.
他会来的
Well, he'll show up.
说吧  到底怎么了
Hey, come on, what's really wrong?
昨晚我做了一个梦
I had one of those dreams last night.
- 跟他有关  - 也不尽然
- About him? - Well, not exactly.
但是
It's that...
我觉得自己失控了
I just felt like I wasn't in control.
这是那件事结束后的第一次
For the first time since all that.
听着  只要你没梦到他
Look, if you don't dream him up,
他伤害不了你和我们  记得吗
he can't hurt you or us, remember?
- 你说得对  - 这就对了
- You're right. - There you go.
- 我爱你  - 我爱你
- Love you. - I love you.
丹
Hey, Dan, Dan.
- 艾莉丝  - 嗨
- Alice. - Hi.
- 你今天好漂亮  - 谢谢
- You look sweet today. - Thank you.
- 亲爱的  - 嗨
- Hi, darling. - Hi.
丹  这位是奥斯卓教练  下个星期他要做面试
Dan, this is Coach Ostrow. He's interviewing next week.
本州最棒的四分卫  你知道大家是怎么说的
Finest quarterback in the state. You know what they say.
这孩子的速度飞快
This boy feels the need for speed.
我听说了
So I've heard.
爸  我们能待会再谈吗
Um, Dad, could, uh, we get into this later?
我是说暑假才刚开始  我
I mean, summer's just starting and I just...
丹  我们在谈你的未来
Hey, Dan, we're talking about your future here.
对不起  亲爱的
Excuse us, dear.
- 听我说  过来  - 没关系的  丹
- Now, listen, come here. - It's okay, Dan.
- 来吧  - 我们很照顾球员的
- Check it out. - We take care of our boys.
我们还会配车
We got the right cars....
- 笑一个  - 来吧
- Say cheese. - Cheese.
再来一张  来吧
Another one. There you go.
- 真的太棒了  - 好
- That's great. - All right.
恭喜你  艾莉丝
Congratulations, Alice.
你真的好漂亮
You looked beautiful up there.
我以你为荣
I'm so proud of you.
- 天啊  谢谢你  爸  - 你的确很漂亮
- Gee, thanks, Dad. - You do look beautiful.
我还担心你不来了
I was afraid you weren't coming.
我站在后面看
I watched from behind the stands.
我不想害你丢脸
I didn't wanna embarrass you.
大家会说"那个酒鬼来了"
You know, "the drunk showed up." That kind of thing.
那都过去了  除非你不再去参加戒酒会
That's in the past. Unless you've stopped going to your meetings.
不  我们说好的
No. A deal's a deal.
来吧
Come on.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
噢
Oh....
- 拍照  - 我不太上相
- To take a picture. - I don't take good pictures.
嗯
Uh....
- 下班后打电话给我  好吗  - 好
- Call me when your, uh, shift ends, okay? - Okay.
再见
Goodbye, sir.
别担心  八月时我会送她回家
Don't worry. I'll have her home by August.
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
- 待会见  - 再见
- See you later. - Bye.
谢谢你特地赶来  爸
Thanks for everything, Dad.
你确定不需要我送你去上班
You sure you don't want a ride to work?
不用  走过公园就到了
No, it's just across the park.
好吧  今晚玩得开心点
Okay. Have fun tonight.
好
Okay.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
佛莱迪要来抓你了
Freddy's coming for you.
三  四  锁好你的门
Three, four, better lock your door.
五  六  快去拿十字架
Five, six, grab your crucifix.
七  八  彻夜不眠
Seven, eight, better stay up late.
来吧  快跑  我们走
Come on. Run, let's go.
七  八  彻夜不眠
Seven, eight, better stay awake.
九  十  他又回来了
Nine, ten, he's back again.
等一下
Wait.
放开我
Let me go! Let me go!
- 好  压住她  - 冷静点
- All right, now, hold her steady there. - Calm down.
没什么好害怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
照我的话去做
Just do exactly what I say.
不
No!
帮帮我
Help me.
为什么这一切又发生了
Why is this happening again?
拜托  别让他这么做
Oh, please don't let him do this.
别惊慌  亚曼达
Don't panic, Amanda.
你的胎位不正  宝宝臀部朝下
We have a breech birth here. It's backward.
- 啊 - 我们得把宝宝转过来
- Aah! - We're going to have to turn it around.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
我要你用力  用力
I'm gonna need you to push. Now push.
用力
Push. Push.
天啊
Holy shit.
这是什么东西
What is it?
小心
Careful.
姊妹  这是上帝的创造物
Sister, this is one of God's creatures.
你得那样安慰自己
Take solace in that.
那不是上帝的创造物
That is no creature of God.
住手  快把他交给我
Stop it. Give it to me.
- 小心  - 别让他逃了
- Watch it. - Don't let it get away.
不  又来了
No! Not again!
是个男孩
It's a boy.
你不可能又回来了
You can't come back.
我把你锁了起来
I locked the door on you.
- 但我找到钥匙了 - 啊
- But I found the key. - Aah!
你的出生是对人类的诅咒
Your birth was a curse on the whole of humanity.
我不会让那种事再度发生
I will not allow it to happen again.
你召唤我回来让你重生  现在我要你的命
You brought me back to give you life, but now I must take yours.
走着瞧吧  臭女人
We'll see, bitch.
走着瞧吧
We'll just see.
- 我必须从我的人间监狱逃出来  - 该怎么做呢
- I must be released from my earthly prison. - How?
到高塔找我
Look for me in the tower.
你永远都找不到她的
You'll never find her.
- 艾莉丝  - 安妮
- Alice. - Anne.
天啊  还好是你  太可怕了
Oh, God, I'm glad it's you. It was terrible.
- 发生了什么事  - 我在梦里
- What happened? - I was in the dream.
我不知道是怎么一回事  但现在他回来了
And I don't know how, but now he's back.
我以为你死了  你迟到四小时
I thought you were dead. You're four hours late.
四小时
Four hours?
不论你有什么毛病  我希望我能开药治好你
I wish I had a prescription for whatever it is you're on.
什么
What?
听着  谢谢你了  艾莉丝  再见
Listen, thanks a lot, Alice, for nada.
我来了
Bombs away.
好吧
All right.
你跟艾莉丝要去欧洲的事  你爸怎么说
What did your dad say about you and Alice going to Europe?
没事  他只是叫个不停  试着说服我相信我在虚掷人生
Nothing. Just screamed a lot and tried to convince me I'm throwing my life away.
- 谁在虚掷人生  - 丹  他要跟艾莉丝去旅行
- Who's throwing their life away? - Dan, and he's taking Alice with him.
跳得好  伊芳  你一直都有练习
Pretty good dive, Yvonne. You've been practicing.
没错  每天两小时  每星期六天
That's right. Two hours a day, six days a week.
再喝一瓶  你会需要的
Have another one. You need it.
不  再过两小时我得上班  你何不下水呢
No, I got a shift in a couple of hours. Aren't you going in?
不  我妈找了一个混蛋摄影师  到家里吃晚餐
No, my mom's got this asshole jerk-off photographer coming over to dinner...
我不该把头发弄乱
...and I'm not supposed to mess up my hair.
你不厌倦你妈老在命令你该做什么吗
Hey, aren't you sick of your mom trying to run your life?
- 是啊  - 别让他们那么做
- Yeah. - Don't let them.
当然  没问题
Sure, no problem.
他说得对  有时候我觉得我跟墨利刻耳忒斯住在一起
You know, he's right. Sometimes I feel like I'm living with Melicertes.
- 谁  - 谁
- Who? - Who?
墨利刻耳忒斯  他是我在书上看到的古人
Melicertes. He's this ancient guy I read about, right?
他杀了他的孩子
Who, like, killed his kids...
因为他不喜欢他们统治王国的方式
...because he didn't like the way they were running the kingdom.
你真的很奇怪  你知道吗
You're really weird, you know that?
别提他们了  开香槟  我们得大玩一场
Screw them. Open the champagne. Let's have a party.
- 好吧  - 不  那是待会我跟艾莉丝要喝的
- All right. - No, no, that's for Alice and me later.
抱歉
Sorry.
- 你没事吧  - 天啊
- Are you okay? - Oh, my God.
天啊  我一整晚都会想到那一幕
Oh, God, I could have gone all night without looking at that.
我觉得这真的很奇怪  你画的漫画
I think it's very strange how you draw all your comics...
- 都是鲜血淋漓的画面 - 啊
- ...Ioaded with blood and guts. - Ugh.
但你害怕看到血
That freaks you out.
对  只是一点血而已  兄弟
Yeah, it's just a little blood, guy.
我知道那是什么  大笨蛋
I know what it is, you big, dumb jock.
丹
Yo, Dan.
丹  有你的电话  来吧
Dan, telephone. Come on.
我马上回来  别碰这个  好吗
I'll be right back. Don't touch this, okay?
好的  我们会用生命保护它
Okay, we'll guard it with our lives.
丹  是克鲁格
Dan, it was Krueger.
- 什么  - 那发生在我清醒的时候
- What? - lt happened while I was awake.
- 你了解我在说什么吗  - 等一下  怎么会
- Do you understand what I'm saying? - Wait a second, how could...
他一定是梦到了自己  我不知道
He must have dreamt himself up. I don't know.
天啊  丹  我好害怕
Jesus, Dan, I'm scared.
好吧  待在那里
All right, stay right there.
- 我马上到  - 好  我等你
- I'm on my way. - Okay, I will.
- 快一点  好吗  - 好  再见
- Just hurry, okay? - Okay, bye.
该死
Shit.
发生了什么事  有人死了吗
What happened? Somebody die?
- 不  我得走了  - 艾莉丝召见
- No, I gotta go. - Alice beckons.
罗密欧  你忘了你的秘密武器
Hey, Romeo, you forgot the secret ingredient.
他走了  速度最快的三腿男
There he goes, the fastest man on three legs.
春木市之音
SK, the sounds of Springwood.
今晚春木市的市区天气不错
It's a beautiful evening here in downtown Springwood...
我们马上为大家带来好听的音乐
...and we'll be back with the music in just a moment.
首先要接听大家的来电
Right now, we're open for your calls.
请说吧  你已经上线
So go ahead, you're on the air.
我要抱怨一下  跟我断绝关系的任性儿子丹尼尔
I'm calling about my wayward ex-son Daniel...
他一直像个不知感激的混蛋
... who's been acting like an ungrateful dickweed...
自从那个波霸浪女艾莉丝勾引了他之后
... ever since he was seduced by that bimbo slut whore Alice.
妈
Mom?
女士  我建议你杀了那个不知感激的小鬼
If I were you, lady, I'd kill the ungrateful piggy.
加快马力  丹
Put your pedal to the metal, Dan.
运气不好  丹
Bad year, Dan.
系上安全带  亲爱的
Better buckle up, dear.
这孩子速度真的很快
This boy feels the need for speed.
逮到你了
Gotcha.
燃料注入
Fuel injection.
动力全开
Power drive.
快车道
Fast lane.
丹尼  开车时不要做梦
Hey, Danny, better not dream and drive.
- 请给我咖啡  谢谢  - 没问题
- Coffee, please? - Yeah.
艾莉丝
Alice!
丹
Dan!
不
No!
他突然间冲出来
He just came fucking flying out of nowhere.
车子冲了出来
It was some kind of a frigging jet.
我根本没看到他
I didn't even see him.
你好  艾莉丝
Hi, Alice.
你要跟我生孩子吗
You wanna make babies?
丹
Dan.
你没事
You're all right.
没事的  甜心  我在这里
It's okay, honey, I'm right here.
艾莉丝  丹发生了车祸
Alice, Dan's been in an accident.
那不是车祸  是克鲁格
It was no accident. It was Krueger.
以前他会透过我的梦现身  现在不一样了
He used to come in through my dreams and not anymore.
他找到其他的方法
He found some other way.
不  艾莉丝  对不起
No, Alice, I'm sorry.
这不是梦
But it was no dream.
丹死了
Dan's dead.
不  丹没死
No. Not Dan.
他抓走丹了
He got Dan.
甜心  我很抱歉
Honey, I'm so sorry.
爸  那不是意外  克鲁格杀了丹
Daddy, it wasn't an accident. Krueger killed Dan.
冷静下来  放轻松  你是惊吓过度
Calm down, take it easy. You're in shock.
警察发现香槟瓶碎片
The police found fragments of a champagne bottle.
丹不喝酒  你知道的
Dan didn't drink. You know that.
或许他是要跟我一起庆祝我们的旅行
I mean, it was probably for me to celebrate our trip.
- 我们得想想办法  - 艾莉丝
- I mean, we gotta do something. - Alice.
丹已经死了  你还不懂吗  他又来了
Dan's already dead, don't you see? It's starting again.
这样的失控并不罕见
These sorts of outbursts aren't entirely uncommon.
许多女性一开始都会这样
Many women have them at the beginning.
特别是她们受到重创的时候
Especially if they have suffered a traumatic shock.
别担心  小妹妹  你会没事的
Don't worry, young lady. You're gonna be fine.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
他在胡说什么
What's he talking about?
我是怎么了
What's wrong with me?
没事
Nothing.
你怀孕了
You're just a little pregnant.
医生要整晚监控你
The doctor wants to keep you overnight.
这是例行观察
Just for routine observation...
确定让你舒服点
...to make sure you're as comfortable as possible.
你会没事的  甜心
You're gonna be fine, honey.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be okay.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hello.
- 你叫什么名字  - 雅各
- What's your name? - Jacob.
真的  我一直都喜欢那个名字
Really? I've always loved that name.
你该回你的房间吧  雅各
Shouldn't you be in your room, Jacob?
那里真的好寂寞
It's lonely there.
- 我叫做  - 我很遗憾你的男朋友死了
- Well, my name is... - I'm sorry your boyfriend got killed.
你怎么知道
How did you know that?
我看得出来你很悲伤
I could tell you were sad.
我只是想知道你是否没事
I just wanted to see if you were all right.
雅各  等一下  别走
Jacob, wait. Don't go.
葛芮姐  亲爱的  你该睡美容觉了
Greta, dear, it's time to get your beauty sleep.
我不希望你的漂亮双眼出现黑眼圈
We don't want circles under those beautiful eyes.
好
Okay, okay.
你看过跟我同楼层的那个小男孩吗
Have you visited that little boy on my floor?
他叫雅各
You know, Jacob?
他的眼神看起来很悲伤
He has kind of, um, sad eyes.
没有小男孩跟你住同一层楼
There aren't any little boys on your floor.
他一定是从儿童病房溜出来的
Well, he must have wandered in from the children's ward.
我很好奇他到底是怎么了
I was just wondering what's wrong with him.
我们没有儿童病房
We don't have a children's ward.
他穿着病人服
Well, he was wearing a hospital robe.
我不知道该怎么跟你说
I don't know what to tell you.
- 你打电话给大家了吗  - 有
- Well, did you call everyone? - Yup.
听着  做梦的事  就当是你跟我的秘密  好吗
Listen, um, let's keep this dream stuff between you and me, okay?
亚曼达·克鲁格是神职人员
Amanda Krueger was part of a religious order...
1940年代在那家精神病院工作
...that ran that asylum in the 1940s.
她被神经病强暴  在那里生下孩子
She was raped by lunatics and had the baby there.
那孩子就是佛莱迪·克鲁格
That baby grew up to be Freddy Krueger...
在榆树街这里杀了二十到三十个小孩
...who murdered 20 or 30 kids right here on Elm Street.
警方逮捕他  但他因为技术问题无罪开释
He got caught, but the courts cut him loose on a technicality.
死掉小孩的爸妈一起合作杀了他
So the parents of the murdered kids got together and killed him.
把他烧死
Torched him.
但那只是开始
But that was just the beginning.
他继续杀人
He keeps on killing.
他在他们的恶梦里行凶
But he kills people in their dreams, their nightmares.
他利用我的梦  让他对受害者下手
He uses my dreams to bring him his victims.
丹的死全都是我的错
It's my fault that Dan's dead.
别再那么说了  那是胡说八道
Stop saying that. That's bullshit.
我们谈谈宝宝的事
Let's talk about the baby.
对  恭喜你
Yeah, congratulations.
- 我想是吧  - 那不是我们见面的原因
- I guess. - That's not what we're here for.
丹的爸妈一直在逼他
Dan's parents were really pushing him hard.
他在派对上抱怨  他的压力很大
He was bitching about it at the party. He was under a lot of pressure.
- 我们都一样  - 霸道的爸妈会把孩子逼疯
- We all are. - Pushy parents can drive you nuts.
那跟这件事有什么关系
What does that have to do with it?
丹死的时候  你根本没在睡觉
When Dan died, you weren't even asleep.
那是你说的  说那么简单
You even said so. End of story.
他一定找到别的办法了
He must have found some other way.
听我说
Listen to me.
这不是开玩笑
This isn't some kind of joke.
他可以进入我的梦
He gets in through my dreams somehow.
我以为我可以控制  但有些事改变了
And I thought I could control it, but something's changed...
我不知道接下来他会做什么
...and I don't know what he'll do next.
听着  艾莉丝  我们知道你很难过
Look, Alice, we all know you're upset.
艾莉丝  重点是如果有人要伤害你
The bottom line, Alice if anybody's trying to hurt you...
不论是不是超自然力量  他们都得先过我们这一关
...supernatural or not, they're gonna have to go through us first.
我们是一块的  对吧
All of us. Right?
我就担心会是那样
That's what I'm afraid of.
戒酒会还好吧
How was the meeting?
- 我很清醒  - 很好笑
- Sobering. - Very funny.
- 艾莉丝  - 你什么时候会聪明购物了
- Alice... - When did you become a smart shopper?
自从我女儿要当妈妈后
Ever since my little girl became a mom.
你对我失望吗
You disappointed in me?
不
No.
不  我没有那么想
No, I'm not.
我希望是个男孩
I sort of hope it's a boy.
家里再出现男孩玩乐的声音应该会是件好事
It'd be nice to hear a boy playing around in the house again.
但别把这当成习惯了
Just don't make a habit of it.
真的  大家老把我们误认为姊妹
It's true. People are always mistaking us for sisters. Ha, ha.
葛芮姐的身材很适合当模特儿
Greta certainly has the perfect body for modeling.
- 艾琳·福特是我的朋友 - 哦
- You know, Eileen Ford is a friend of mine. - Ooh.
我跟她提过你
I told her about you.
她非常有兴趣
She's very interested.
葛芮姐  这是毕生难逢的机会
Greta, you're being offered the opportunity of a lifetime.
我想你该表达一下谢意
I think you should show a little gratitude.
妈  昨天我朋友死了
One of my friends died yesterday, Mother.
你介意我花几小时哀悼他吗
Do you mind if I take a few hours off to remember him?
我们在办晚宴  亲爱的
But we're having a party, dear.
我看到报导了
I read about him.
他喝醉了  对吧
Drunk or something, wasn't he?
他只是葛芮姐的朋友
Oh, he was just a friend of Greta's.
他们的关系不特别  他们没有在交往
Not someone special. Not someone she was seeing.
你了解的
You understand.
不  谢谢  我不饿
No thank you. I'm not hungry.
你不吃吗
Aren't you eating?
我不想吃
I really don't feel up to it.
真的  亲爱的  你该吃点东西
Really, dear, you ought to try something.
是你一直要我注意体重  妈
You're the one who's always slapping my hand about my weight, Mother.
所以我们才节食  亲爱的
That's why we diet, dear...
我们才能在宴会上吃东西不会让其他宾客不愉快
...so we can eat at social events and not upset the other guests.
听我说
Tell you what.
我何不把整盘东西吃掉
Why don't I just eat the whole goddamn tray...
再跑去吐  等一下再回来呢
...go throw up, and come back for seconds, all right?
夫人  让我来吧
Madame, if I may.
祝你用餐愉快  笨女孩
Bon appetit, bitch.
芭比娃娃排
Mm. Fillet de Barbie. Ha, ha.
葛芮姐只要最好的
Nothing but the best for Greta.
张开嘴巴
Open wide.
我来帮你
Second helping.
吃东西时别说话  亲爱的
Don't talk with your mouth full, dear.
你吃的东西会成为你的一部分
You are what you eat.
可怜的孩子  好了
Oh, poor baby. There.
葛芮姐
Greta.
爸
Dad.
爸  快来帮忙
Dad, help.
葛芮姐
Greta?
甜心  晚餐煮好了吗
Honey? How's dinner coming?
我不敢相信会发生这种事
I can't believe this shit is happening.
撑着点  伊芳
Just hang in there, Yvonne.
天啊  我知道马克一定吓坏了
Man, I know Mark is gonna be wigging out.
我们得撑下来
We just gotta keep tight.
我们会挺过去的  好吗
We'll get through, okay?
我知道他就在这附近  女孩们  我想他真的很难过
I know he's back here somewhere, girls. I think he's pretty upset.
马克
Mark.
嗨
Hey.
- 马克  你没事吧  - 我没事  只是很难过
- Mark, are you okay? - I'm fine, just aces.
我要跟你们谈谈葛芮姐的事
I wanna talk to you guys about Greta.
我很抱歉  但葛芮姐今天死了
Oh, I'm terribly sorry, but Greta's dead today.
或许我们该谈谈别人的事
Perhaps we could, uh, interest you in someone else.
- 听着  那是意外  跟丹一样  - 那不是意外
- Look, it was an accident, just like Dan's. - No accident.
我跟你们警告过克鲁格的事
I tried to warn all of you about Krueger.
- 艾莉丝  拜托  - 我想过那一点
- Alice, please. - I thought about that.
她一定是在吃饭时睡着了
She must have fallen asleep while she was at the table.
- 这真的很变态  各位  - 太可怕了
- This is getting a little sick, guys. - Too bad.
我不了解发生了什么事
I don't understand what's happening.
克鲁格得利用我的梦
Krueger has to use my dreams...
但他在我清醒时杀了丹跟葛芮姐
...but he got to Dan and Greta while I was awake.
他是怎么办到的
How's he doing it?
- 你们两个为什么不能面对现实  - 你何不闭嘴听她说呢
- Why don't you two stick to reality? - Why don't you shut up and let her talk.
两天内我们之中死了两个人
Two of us have died in the past two days.
你觉得那很正常吗
Does that strike you as particularly normal?
- 马克  - 我还没有说完
- Mark... - I'm not finished.
我非常爱葛芮姐
I loved Greta, a lot.
如果有人或有股力量杀了她
And if maybe, just maybe, someone or something killed her...
我要知道真相
...I'd Iike to hear about it.
- 我不想再听这些废话了  - 那就给我滚
- I'm not gonna listen to this anymore. - Then get out.
别这样
Hey, come on.
伊芳  等一下  对不起
Yvonne, wait a minute, wait a minute. I'm sorry.
我是个混蛋  好吗
I'm an asshole, okay?
我知道我处理得不太好
I know I'm not dealing with this very well...
但这不是你的错
...but it's not your fault, and, uh....
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
没关系的
It's okay. Ha, ha.
你能留下来吗
You stick around for a while?
我真的想留下来  可是
I wish I could, but, uh....
今晚我有班  我得走了
I got a shift tonight. I gotta get going.
如果你要的话  我可以留下来陪你
I'll stay with you for a while, if you want.
- 大家再见  - 好
- Bye, you guys. - Yeah.
再见
See you.
你觉得我是个白痴才会爱上她吗
Do you think I'm an idiot for being in love with her?
没有人那么想
Nobody thinks that.
我知道我根本没机会  可是
I mean, I know I didn't stand a chance in hell, but...
她非常在乎你
She cared a lot about you.
或许是她妈害死她
Well, maybe it was her mother who killed her...
因为她要求她必须完美
...with all that Polly Perfect shit.
这跟她妈无关
It wasn't her mother.
今晚我们邀请到这些混蛋
We have these scumbags here on the hot seat tonight.
魅影幽魂不会害怕跟她说出他心里的感觉
The Phantom Prowler wouldn't have been afraid to tell her how he felt.
真希望我有他十分之一的胆识
If I only had a 10th of his guts.
天啊  他并不存在  但他比我完美多了
Jesus, he's not even real and he's more of a human being than I am.
这家伙不是你的漫画人物  马克
This guy isn't one of your comic book characters, Mark.
他不是魅影幽魂  他真的存在
He's not the Phantom Prowler. He's for real.
告诉我克鲁格的事
Tell me more about this Krueger guy.
你似乎很累了
You look tired.
我帮你煮杯咖啡好吗
Why don't I make some coffee?
该说的事太多了
There's a Iot to tell.
马克
Mark?
马克  不
Mark, no.
马克
Mark?
救命啊
Help!
- 马克  - 救命啊
- Mark? - Help!
马克  抓住我的手  快点
Mark, take my hand. Take it.
我们得离开这里
We gotta get out of here.
马克  快点
Mark, come on.
该死
Aw. Oh, shit.
雅各
Jacob?
你好
Oh, hello.
嗨
Hi.
你的气色不太好
You don't look very well.
你还好吗
Are you feeling all right?
我一直在做恶梦
Been having bad dreams.
你住在这里吗  雅各
Is this where you live, Jacob?
我在等人
Just waiting for someone.
葛芮姐的事真的很惨
It's sad about Greta.
你在等她吗
Is that who you're waiting for?
不是
No.
我觉得你不该待在这里
I don't think this is a very nice place for you to be.
或许我们该去找你妈妈
Maybe we should go look for your mom.
她不要我
She doesn't want me around.
我相信那不是真的
Oh, I'm sure that's not true.
我敢说她非常担心
I'll bet she's very worried about you.
- 我就会  - 不  你才不会
- I would be. - No, you're not.
你甚至不在乎你要当妈妈了
You don't even care about being a mom.
为什么你没有想到我呢
How come you don't think about me?
- 谁说我  什么  - 我喜欢你
- Who said I... What? - I like you.
我要跟你在一起
I wanna stay with you.
为什么你不喜欢我
How come you don't like me?
谁说我不喜欢你
Who said I don't like you?
我那个有怪手的朋友
My friend with the funny hand.
来吧  甜心  我们得离开这里
Come on, honey. We're gonna get out of here.
不  我得走了  他在叫我
No, I have to go now. He's calling me.
雅各  等一下
Jacob, wait.
雅各
Jacob.
该死
Holy shit.
他真的存在  对吧
He's really real, isn't he?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
他对我的宝宝做了一些事  我知道
He's doing something to my baby. I know it.
他要伤害雅各
He's trying to hurt Jacob.
- 雅各是谁  - 我的宝宝
- Who's Jacob? - My baby.
什么  你已经帮他取名字了
What, you named him already?
对  我想是的
Yeah. I guess so.
我得离开这里  到克鲁格找不到他的地方
I gotta get away from here. Someplace where Krueger can't find him.
哇啊
Whoa.
等一下
Slow down.
你怎能甩掉那个家伙
Now, how you gonna hide from a guy like that? Huh?
- 离开地球表面  - 我不知道
- Leave the planet? - I don't know.
听着  如果你担心宝宝
Look, if you're worried about your baby...
打电话给伊芳  请她找医生帮你检查
...call Yvonne and have the doctor check him out.
我要去查一下克鲁格的资料
I'm gonna go see what else I can find out about Krueger.
- 你吓坏我了  发生了什么事  - 克鲁格想伤害宝宝
- You had me scared. What's wrong? - Krueger's trying to do something to him.
艾莉丝  甜心  不  我爱你  但你得控制一下自己
Alice. Honey, no. I love you, but you're gonna have to get a hold of yourself.
马克知道我没有发疯
Mark knows I'm not crazy.
要他让你看看他的手
Ask him to show you his hands.
我想你需要冷静下来
I think you just need to calm down, okay?
我不知道他是如何在我清醒时杀人
What I can't figure out is how he's getting in when I'm awake.
(产前检查室)
未出生的胎儿会做梦吗
Do unborn babies dream?
对  他们会做梦
Yeah. They do.
答应我一件事
But do us both a favor.
别跟摩尔医生提这件事
Don't mention any of this to Dr. Moore.
艾莉丝
Alice.
我不敢相信你为了这件事要我在星期天早上找摩尔医生来
I can't believe you had me drag Dr. Moore down here on a Sunday morning for this.
对不起  伊芳
I'm sorry, Yvonne.
我觉得这件事很重要
I thought it was something serious.
如果这还不够重要  我不知道这到底是怎么回事
If this isn't serious, I don't know what is.
什么都别说  你会害我被开除的
Don't dare say a word. You're gonna get me fired.
摩尔医生  未出生的胎儿会做梦吗
Dr. Moore, do unborn babies dream?
胎儿在发展时  每天有七成的时间
As the fetus develops, it can spend up to 70 percent of its day...
处在做梦状态
...in a dream state.
越大做梦时间越多
More as it matures.
- 我会感觉到宝宝的梦吗  - 艾莉丝
- Will I be able to sense them? - Alice.
那是你来这里的原因吗
Is that why you're here?
你想知道你的宝宝  是不是在做恶梦
To see if your baby's having nightmares?
我们是来做检查的  对吧
We're here to find out everything we can, aren't we?
老实说我找不到任何理由  在你这个怀孕阶段
Frankly, I have found nothing about you that would indicate the necessity...
帮你做超音波检查
...of ultrasound at this stage of your pregnancy.
我只是要确定宝宝没事
I just wanna make sure my baby's all right.
心跳很强烈
Well, the heart seems strong.
来看一下
Let's hear it.
(病人：艾莉丝·强森 | 医生：摩尔)
这是你的宝宝
There's your baby
帮她冲洗一下照片
Get her file.
看到他跟他爸爸有多像了吧
See any family resemblance? Ha-ha-ha.
喂奶时间到了
Feeding time.
我儿子要吃的灵魂食物
Soul food for my boy.
别碰他
Don't touch him.
他对我的宝宝做了什么
What's he doing to my baby?
拜托  小姐  冷静点
Please, young lady, try to keep calm.
你的宝宝很正常
Your baby is perfectly healthy.
现在看起来是有点大  但我认为还算正常
A little large for so early on, but as normal as I've ever seen.
他夺走他们的灵魂跟意识  要做出跟他一样的宝宝
He's taking their souls, their spirits, and making the baby like him.
听着  甜心  你累了
Look, sweetie, you're tired.
我带你回家后  你会舒服点的  好吗
You'll feel better after I take you home and rest, okay?
来吧  我们走
Come on, let's go.
来吧
Come on.
葛芮姐跟丹在那里
Greta and Dan were there.
克鲁格杀了他们
Krueger killed them.
现在他拿他们喂雅各
Now, he was feeding them to Jacob.
艾莉丝
Alice.
艾莉丝  别再那么催眠自己  你知道你在说什么吗
Alice, stop and listen to yourself. Do you know what you sound like?
我知道这听起来很疯狂  但我没疯
Completely insane, but I'm not.
如果你是我的朋友  你会相信我
And if you're my friend, you would believe me a little.
我是你的朋友  我很担心你
I am your friend, and I'm worried sick about you.
你该抛开那些怪想法  好好面对事实了
It's time to leave the Twilight Zone and face reality.
- 克鲁格真的存在  - 你的宝宝也一样
- Krueger is reality. - So is your baby.
- 你得为自己着想  - 你以为我在做什么
- You got more to think about than yourself. - What do you think I'm doing?
听着  信不信由你  克鲁格回来了
Look, whether you believe it or not, Krueger is back.
他找上我的宝宝  如果我不救他  谁能救他呢
He's after my baby, and if I don't try to do something about it, who will?
你一副发疯的样子帮不了你自己或你的宝宝
You're not doing yourself or your baby any good by acting like a crazy woman.
你何不离开呢
Why don't you take off?
离开春木市  冷静一下
Leave Springwood. Cool off for a while.
伊芳  你无法逃离这家伙的魔掌
Goddamn it, you don't just run away from this guy.
他会在你的梦里找到你
He finds you in your dreams.
他找上我们之前已经杀了很多人
He found a lot of other people before he found us.
- 你也一样  - 昨晚他邀请我去他家
- You too? - He invited me to his house last night.
听着  我们都累了  星期五晚上后我们都没睡好
Look, we're all tired, and we haven't had any sleep since Friday night.
- 那是你还活着的唯一原因  - 不  才不是
- That's the only reason you're alive. - No, it's not.
伊芳  看一下这些东西  好吗
Yvonne, look through this stuff, will you?
她没发疯
She's not crazy.
你还好吧
You okay?
我知道接下来会发生什么事
I know what's happening.
克鲁格利用雅各的梦
Krueger's using Jacob's dreams.
我们得阻止他
We gotta stop him.
有一个办法
Well, there is one way.
你有想过不生下宝宝吗
Have you thought about not having the baby?
我是说没有宝宝  宝宝就不会做梦
I mean, no baby, no baby's dreams.
不  我不能那么做
No, I can't do that.
我看到他在我的身体里成长
I saw him inside of me growing.
他是我跟丹的一部分  我想留下他
He's part of me and Dan. I wanna keep him.
好吧  我们另外再想办法
Okay, then we'll find another way.
我看过她
I've seen her.
艾莉丝  你能下楼来一下吗
Alice, can you come down a minute?
嗨
Oh, hi.
艾莉丝
Alice.
乔登先生跟我想过来看看你
Mr. Jordan and I wanted to see how you're feeling.
坐吧
Well, come sit down.
现在不是好时候  或许你们得改天再来
This really isn't a good time. Maybe you could come back.
老实说  我们想知道  你打算怎么处理宝宝
Frankly, we wondered what you intend to do with your baby.
什么
What I what?
我想过了  我要留下宝宝
Well, I've thought about it and I plan to keep him.
我们担心这对你来说  可能负担太大了
We were concerned that all this might be a little bit too much for you.
你得当单亲妈妈
I mean, being single and everything.
乔登先生的意思是我们知道
What Mr. Jordan means is that we're aware of the burden...
要你带大孩子的压力有多大
...that raising a child would place on you.
我们想要帮忙
We want to help.
我们想领养宝宝  把他视如己出
We want to adopt it and to raise it as though it were our own.
听着  我了解你们的用心  但不行
Look, I appreciate what you're offering, but, no.
他是我的责任
He's my responsibility.
他也是我们的责任
And ours.
他是我们的孙子
It's our grandchild.
桃乐丝  或许这不是个好点子
Doris, maybe this wasn't such a good idea.
听着  艾莉丝  我们担心你现在的状况
Look, Alice, we're worried that in your present condition...
怕你没有能力照顾宝宝
...that you don't have the ability to take care of a child.
你说我的状况怎么了
What are you talking about, my condition?
摩尔医生打电话给我们
We got a call from Dr. Moore.
他说艾莉丝歇斯底里  出现了偏执幻想
He said that Alice was hysterical and that she was having paranoid delusions.
你们不了解
You don't understand.
我们知道你吃了很多苦
We know you've been through a lot...
但现在的重点不只是你的感受
...but there is more at stake here than just your feelings.
你们不能带走我的宝宝
You're not taking my baby.
- 或许法官不会同意你的说法  - 我支持她
- Well, the courts might not agree with you. - But I do.
我听够你们的胡官乱语了
I've heard enough of this crap.
你以为你们能跑到我家  威胁我女儿
You think you can just walk into my house and threaten my daughter?
拜托  我们在法律上有权这么做
Oh, please, we have a legitimate claim to it.
他不是一样东西
He's not a thing.
他是我的一部分  我不会把他交给你们或其他人
He's part of me, and I'm not giving him to you or anyone else.
他们认为我疯了
They think I'm nuts.
那是他们的问题
That's their problem.
不  那是我们的问题  马克
No, it's our problem, Mark.
如果我不把问题处理掉  或许他们真的会把雅各带走
If I don't deal with this, they really might try to take Jacob.
- 你说她是自杀  - 对  报纸是那么说的
- You said she committed suicide. - Yeah, that's what the papers thought.
她一辈子都待在精神病院
She spent the rest of her life in the asylum.
克鲁格案落幕后  她抓狂了  他们认为她是上吊自杀
After Krueger's trial, she flipped out, and hung herself, so they thought.
- 所以呢  - 他们无法证实
- Meaning? - Meaning they couldn't prove it.
找不到尸体
No body.
但我看到她的坟墓
But I've seen her grave.
可能是衣冠塚
Uh, empty plot.
让人有地方可以追思她
A memorial stone.
空坟  他们没有真的埋葬她
Vacant. They never put her under.
很酷吧
Cool, huh?
我不了解
I don't understand.
如果她是自杀  她的灵魂还在受苦
If she killed herself, her soul is gonna be in torment.
你从哪里听来的
Where'd you hear that?
就是这本书  里面有写到
Right here, somewhere.
有了"轮回"
Yeah. "Transmigration."
"罪人的灵魂"
"Soul of the sinner."
找到了"被困在人间的安息地"
Yeah, yeah. "Trapped in its earthly resting place."
在梦里她试着阻止他
In the dream, she was trying to stop him.
她告诉我该怎么做  然后门关上了
She started to tell me how, then the door slammed.
一定是他干的
He must have done it.
我们得查出她在哪里死掉  释放她的灵魂
We have to find where she died to release her soul.
我要你保持清醒  看着我  好吗
I want you to stay awake and watch me, okay?
没问题
Hey, no problem.
你没来练习
Hey, you missed practice.
发生了什么事  你谈恋爱了吗
What happened? Did you fall in love or something?
别问那么多
Don't ask.
你根本不想知道
You don't even wanna know.
泳池还开放着吗
Is the pool still open?
快一点的话  你应该能赶上
I think if you hurry.
亚曼达
Amanda!
嘿  艾莉丝
Hey, Alice.
我们来玩玩吧
Let's rock 'n' roll.
你要去哪里  小可爱
Where are you going, piglet? Ha, ha.
派对才刚刚开始
The party's just starting.
我知道你要做什么
I know exactly what you're up to.
我想我要对伊芳下手
I thought I was up to, uh, Yvonne.
你何不闭嘴
Why don't you just shut up.
发生了什么事
What happened?
因为亚曼达的关系  他不敢进来
He's scared to come in because of Amanda.
你没事吧
Hey, are you all right?
- 天啊  - 对
- Oh, God. - Yeah.
你没发疯
You're not crazy.
我们得找到亚曼达  她是关键
We have to find Amanda. She's the key.
来吧
Come on. Come on.
(来自地狱的恶梦)
(艾莉丝)
天啊
Jesus.
艾莉丝
Alice!
不
No.
不会吧
No. No.
- 不 - 哈哈哈
- No! - Ha-ha-ha.
- 马克  救救我  拜托 - 哈哈
- Mark, help me, please. - Ha, ha.
- 葛芮姐  - 她真的很美味吧  还是我疯了
- Greta? - ls she delicious or am I crazy?
- 别碰她  - 你也来试试看吧
- You leave her alone. - Try some.
去死吧  你这个丑八怪
Time to die, you scar-faced limp-dick.
比疯狂混蛋还快
Faster than a bastard maniac.
比神经病狂人还有力
More powerful than a loco madman.
我是超级佛莱迪
It's Super Freddy.
我就说  看漫画对你没什么帮助
Told you comic books was bad for you.
马克
Mark!
不
No!
天啊  该死
Oh, God. Oh, shit.
该死  那个房间里发生的事太不对劲了
Damn it. Nothing in that room was up to code.
他们两个没死是个奇迹
It's a miracle they both weren't killed.
不  他不会伤害我  需要我活着
No, he won't hurt me. He needs me alive.
谁  她在说谁
Who? What's she talking about?
不  她只是很难过
No one, officer. She's just very upset.
或许你们两个该到局里来一趟
Maybe both of you should come down to the station.
伊芳
Yvonne.
发生了什么事  马克在哪里
What's going on? Where's Mark?
马克睡着了
Mark fell asleep.
克鲁格杀了他
Krueger got him.
不  天啊
No. God.
好了  我要你坚强一点
Hey, hey, come on. I need you to be strong now.
听着  我们得阻止克鲁格  不让他再对雅各下手
Listen, we have to get to Krueger before he gets to Jacob again.
我们该怎么阻止他
How do we stop him?
通过亚曼达
Through Amanda.
我们得找到她
So we have to find her?
对
Yeah.
别要我再跟那家伙一起进按摩浴缸
Just don't ask me to take a Jacuzzi with that guy again.
他试着用你分散我的注意力时  我人在高塔里
You know, I was in the tower when he used you to distract me.
艾莉丝
Alice.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我要你去我  跟你提过的那家精神病院
I want you to go to the asylum, the one I told you about...
所有事都是从那里开始  到那里找她
...where all of this started and find her.
艾莉丝  你得跟我回家
Alice, Alice, you're coming home with me.
不  爸  我有事要做
No, Dad, I've got something to do.
- 艾莉丝  你得立刻跟我回家  - 爸
- Alice, you're coming with me right now. - Dad.
找到亚曼达  快一点
Find Amanda, and hurry.
快出来  克鲁格
Come on out, Krueger.
游戏结束了
The game's over.
好吧
Okay.
我比你强大
I was stronger than you.
所以你对雅各下手  你这个混蛋
So you picked on Jacob, you bastard.
你要他变得跟你一样  让你可以透过他的梦复活
You're trying to make him like you so you can live through his dreams.
我不会让你那么做
Well, I won't let you.
你听到了吗  克鲁格
You hear me, Krueger?
好吧  如果你不跟我谈  或许会想跟亚曼达谈
Okay, if you won't talk to me, maybe you'd like to talk to Amanda!
出来啊  你这个胆小鬼
Come on, you fucking coward.
晚安  混蛋
Good night, asshole.
我是你真的朋友  雅各
I'm your real friend, Jacob.
就像你的父亲一样
Just like a daddy.
咯吱咯吱
Cootchie-cootchie-coo!
- 咯吱咯吱  - 哈哈
- Cootchie-cootchie-coo! Ha, ha. - Ha, ha.
我要搔你痒
I gotcha. I gotcha.
I gotcha, I gotcha....
- 妈妈  来见见我的朋友 - 哦
- Mommy, meet my friend. - Oh.
做得好  艾莉丝
Nice try, Alice.
谢谢你  宝贝
Thanks, babe.
这是我的新造型  喜欢吗
It's my new look. Like it?
- 妈妈  - 快下楼
- Mommy. - Come downstairs.
他不会伤害你  他需要我们两个
He won't hurt you. He needs us both.
我逮到你们两个了
I've got you both. Ha, ha.
来吧  雅各  该回家了
Come on, Jacob, it's time to go home.
雅各  快跑
Jacob, run!
来吧
Come on, come on.
到爸爸这边来  雅各
Come to Papa. Jacob.
雅各
Jacob.
没事的  儿子
It's all right, son.
丹
Dan?
跟我来
Now, come with me.
雅各  他不是你爸
Jacob, he's not your father!
小孩子  总是让人失望
Kids. Always a disappointment.
好了
Okay.
他在哪里
Where is he?
他躲在你的身体里
Inside you, where he hides.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
他躲在你的身体里
Where he hides out. Inside.
- 所以他找到我  - 怎么会呢
- That's how he found me. - But how?
他说那很容易  因为他太了解你了
He says it's easy because he knows you so well.
好吧  克鲁格  这次我是玩真的
All right, Krueger, this time it's for keeps.
来吧  艾莉丝
Come on, Alice.
现在我们可以好好认识彼此
Now we can really get to know each other.
谢谢
Thank you.
去死吧
Get out.
雅各
Jacob.
雅各  艾莉丝赢不了
Jacob, Alice will not triumph.
现在只有你能帮她
Only you can help her now.
放了她
Hey, leave her.
走吧  我要跟你好好学
Let's go. I wanna learn stuff from you.
她一点都不好玩
She's no fun anymore.
你要教我吗
Teach me? Ha, ha.
就是现在  雅各
Now, Jacob.
释放他给你的力量
Unleash the power he has given you.
下课了  克鲁格
School's out, Krueger.
不
No.
退后
Stay back.
带着你的孩子离开
Take your baby and leave.
放我出去
Let me out.
嗨
Hello.
对  小宝贝
Yeah, little sweetheart.
- 你做得很好  艾莉丝  - 丹也是
- You did good work, Alice. - So did Dan.
- 他还是让你没办法好好睡觉  - 没关系
- ls he still keeping you up at night? - Oh, it's okay.
他还有一辈子的时间能睡觉
He has the rest of his life to catch up on his sleep.
对
Yeah.
甜心
Hi, honey.
好好睡吧  雅各·丹尼尔
Sweet dreams, Jacob Daniel.
小可爱
Hey, cutie.
- 我的外孙还好吧  - 嗨
- How's my little grandson? - Hey.
看吧
Look, look.
你饿了吗
Are you hungry?
- 我们都饿了 - 哈哈
- We all are. - Ha, ha.
甜心
Hey, sweetie.